hairboutique.com 2013-11-01

# HairBoutique Privacy Policy

The HairBoutique.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: The Hair Boutique.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. HairBoutique.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: [http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp](http://cts.vresp.com/c/?TACODA/97c75013d4/fc65bc108b/f13f6fdf4c).

Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Supplementation Information

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.

Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. To be removed from HairBoutique.com's mailing list you can send email to [webmaster@hairboutique.com](mailto:webmaster@hairboutique.com)

Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. To change any of the personal information collected in the past email [webmaster@hairboutique.com](mailto:webmaster@hairboutique.com)

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact

HairBoutique.com  
651 N. Plano Rd., Suite 401  
Richardson, TX 75081  
webmaster@hairboutique.com  

| 

| **Daily Hair Tip**  
---  
To protect against potential heat damage to your hair, always use a blow drier on the coolest setting and make sure to apply a good leave in conditioner that will protect the hair shaft from the dryer.
